Faculty of Business Administration fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Centres and Institute files, 1984 - 1994; F-42-3; 84 cm of textual records 11 photographs
  - Enterprise Centre, 1984 - 1991; F-42-3-3; 62 cm of textual records 11 photographs; Physical description: 11 photographs located in F-42-3-3-1-28
    - Enterprise Centre - administrative records, 1984 - 1991; F-42-3-3-1; 30 cm of textual records; Physical description: 11 photographs located in F-42-3-3-1-28
      - Enterprise Centres fall conference, 1986; F-42-3-3-1-9 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - SFU Enterprise Club, 1986; F-42-3-3-1-10 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - Budget, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-11 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - BUS Plan, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-12 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - Correspondence, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-13 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - Funding agreement, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-14 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - Goals and objectives, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-15 (Archival box - standard 42-14)
      - Management meetings, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-1-16 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - SFU Enterprise Centre Advisory Board, 1986 - 1989; F-42-3-3-1-17 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1987; F-42-3-3-1-18 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Quarterly and annual reports, 1987; F-42-3-3-1-19 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence - Continuing Education, 1987; F-42-3-3-1-20 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - PATSCAN, 1987; F-42-3-3-1-21 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Proposals - privatization training, 1987; F-42-3-3-1-22 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - CAFE program, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-1-23 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Youth Employment Strategies Committee, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-1-24 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - SFU Enterprise Centre newsletter - Venture News, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-1-25 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Publicity, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-1-26 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Small Business Consulting Group (SBCG), 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-1-27 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Small Business Consulting Group (SBCG) - photos, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-1-28 (Archival box - small 42-48)
      - Entrepreneur's Club, 1988; F-42-3-3-1-29 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Program plan, 1988; F-42-3-3-1-30 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Budget, 1988; F-42-3-3-1-31 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence - Business Administration, 1988; F-42-3-3-1-32 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Seminars, 1988 - 1990; F-42-3-3-1-33 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1988 - 1991; F-42-3-3-1-34 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1988 - 1991; F-42-3-3-1-35 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1988 - 1991; F-42-3-3-1-36 (Archival box - standard 42-15)
      - Open House guest book, 1989; F-42-3-3-1-37 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Graduate Diploma Program - Task Force Advisory Committee, 1989; F-42-3-3-1-38 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Graduate Diploma Program - questionnaire, 1989; F-42-3-3-1-39 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Graduate Diploma Program - correspondence, 1989; F-42-3-3-1-40 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Faculty of Business Administration newsletter, 1989 - 1990; F-42-3-3-1-41 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Breakthrough Management Series - Price Waterhouse, 1990; F-42-3-3-1-42 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
    - Enterprise Centre - Student Entrepreneur program, 1987 - 1990; F-42-3-3-2; 7 cm of textual records
      - Program course materials, 1987; F-42-3-3-2-1 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - General, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-2-2 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Curriculum development, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-2-3 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Marketing and publicity, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-2-4 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Instructor position, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-2-5 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program correspondence, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-2-6 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Year-to-date budget and expenditure reports, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-2-7 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Funding submissions, 1987 - 1990; F-42-3-3-2-8 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Project summary report, 1988; F-42-3-3-2-9 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program correspondence, 1988 - 1990; F-42-3-3-2-10 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program forms, 1990; F-42-3-3-2-11 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Budget, 1990; F-42-3-3-2-12 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program course materials, 1990; F-42-3-3-2-13 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Evaluations, 1990; F-42-3-3-2-14 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
    - Enterprise Centre - Starting Right the First Time program, 1986 - 1990; F-42-3-3-3; 25 cm of textual records
      Running Right Club
      - Management meetings, 1986; F-42-3-3-3-1 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program brochures, 1986; F-42-3-3-3-2 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Financial assistance, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-3-3 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Program proposals, 1986 - 1987; F-42-3-3-3-4 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1986 - 1989; F-42-3-3-3-5 (Archival box - standard 42-16)
        Open
      - Program brochures, 1987; F-42-3-3-3-6 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Final report, 1987; F-42-3-3-3-7 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Seminar outlines, 1987; F-42-3-3-3-8 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Seminar leaders, vol. 1, 1987; F-42-3-3-3-9 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Seminar leaders, vol. 2, 1987; F-42-3-3-3-10 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - General, vol. 1, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-3-11 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - General, vol. 2, 1987 - 1988; F-42-3-3-3-12 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Financial assistance, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-3-13 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Program correspondence, 1987 - 1989; F-42-3-3-3-14 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Copyright permission, 1987 - 1990; F-42-3-3-3-15 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - General, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-16 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Training Plan, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-17 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Program instructors and evaluations, vol. 1, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-18 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Program instructors and evaluations, vol. 2, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-19 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Awards reception, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-20 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Fraser Valley program, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-21 (Archival box - standard 42-17)
      - Chinese program, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-22 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Chinese program - instructors, 1988; F-42-3-3-3-23 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Program review, 1988 - 1989; F-42-3-3-3-24 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Distance Education, 1988 - 1989; F-42-3-3-3-25 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - General, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-26 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Budget, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-27 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Program forms, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-28 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Awards, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-29 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Program instructors, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-30 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Seminar outlines, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-31 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Program evaluations, vol. 1, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-32 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Program evaluations, vol. 2, 1989; F-42-3-3-3-33 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Copyright permission, 1989 - 1990; F-42-3-3-3-34 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      - Running Right Club, 1989 - 1990; F-42-3-3-3-35 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
- Faculty committees and meeting files, 1982 - 1998; F-42-4; 90 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Dean's correspondence with various campus committees and membership in professional associations. Also included are minutes from Faculty of Business Administration staff meetings and liaison with the External Advisory Board. For the complete list of committees and associations, see the sub-series list below. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports and publications.
  - 25th Anniversary Campus Campaign Committee, 1989 - 1991; F-42-4-1; 1 cm of textual records
    25th Anniversary Committee
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1989 - 1990; F-42-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.18.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990 - 1991; F-42-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
  - Asia Pacific Programme Committee, 1985 - 1986; F-42-4-2; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1985 - 1986; F-42-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
  - Computing and Equipment Committee, 1995 - 1997; F-42-4-3; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1995 - 1997; F-42-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-18)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1982 - 1998; F-42-4-4; 42 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1982; F-42-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1983; F-42-4-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1984; F-42-4-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1984; F-42-4-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1985; F-42-4-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1985; F-42-4-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1986; F-42-4-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1986; F-42-4-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1986; F-42-4-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 42-19)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1987; F-42-4-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1987; F-42-4-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1988; F-42-4-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1989; F-42-4-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990; F-42-4-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1991; F-42-4-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1992; F-42-4-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 42-20)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1993; F-42-4-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1993; F-42-4-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1994; F-42-4-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1994; F-42-4-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1995; F-42-4-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1996; F-42-4-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 42-21)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1997; F-42-4-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1997; F-42-4-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1998; F-42-4-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
  - EMBA Alumni Endowment Committee, 1990 - 1996; F-42-4-5; 3 cm of textual records
    EMBA Alumni Endowment Committee
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990 - 1993; F-42-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1994 - 1996; F-42-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
  - External Advisory Board (EAB), 1992 - 1997; F-42-4-6; 8 cm of textual records
    External Advisory Board
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1992; F-42-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.4.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1993; F-42-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1994; F-42-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-22)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1995; F-42-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1996; F-42-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1997; F-42-4-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
  - External Review Committee, 1988 - 1994; F-42-4-7; 2 cm of textual records
    External Review Committee
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1988 - 1990; F-42-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.5.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1991 - 1994; F-42-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
  - Faculty meetings, 1985 - 1996; F-42-4-8; 10 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1985 - 1989; F-42-4-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.6.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990; F-42-4-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1991; F-42-4-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1992; F-42-4-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1993; F-42-4-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1994; F-42-4-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-23)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1995; F-42-4-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1996; F-42-4-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
  - Nominations Committee, 1988 - 1998; F-42-4-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1988 - 1998; F-42-4-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.8.
  - Pacific Rim Program Advisory Committee, 1983 - 1987; F-42-4-10; 1 cm of textual records
    Pacific Rim Program Advisory Committee
    - Correspondence and reports, 1983 - 1987; F-42-4-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
  - Planning and Priorities Committee, 1993 - 1996; F-42-4-11; 4 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1993 - 1994; F-42-4-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.64.
    - Correspondence and reports, 1995; F-42-4-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1996; F-42-4-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
  - President's Advisory Committee on University Planning, 1990 - 1994; F-42-4-12; 1 cm of textual records
    President's Advisory Committee on University Planning
    - Correspondence and reports, 1990 - 1994; F-42-4-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.29.
  - Senate Committee on International Students, 1992 - 1993; F-42-4-13; 1 cm of textual records
    Senate Committee on International Students
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1992 - 1993; F-42-4-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-24)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.43.
  - Space Committee - West Mall Complex, 1989 - 1991; F-42-4-14; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1989; F-42-4-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.11.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1990; F-42-4-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1991; F-42-4-14-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1991; F-42-4-14-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
  - Trade, Innovation, Competitiveness and Sustainability Committee, 1994 - 1995; F-42-4-15; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1994; F-42-4-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
      Creator's original file classification code: CO.70.
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1995; F-42-4-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1995; F-42-4-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 3, 1995; F-42-4-15-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-25)
- Canadian Federation of Deans of Management and Administrative Studies (CFDMAS) records, 1987 - 1995; F-42-5; 50 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to Dean Stanley Shapiro's tenure as Chairman of the Canadian Federation of Deans of Management and Administrative Studies from 1988 to 1990 and departmental membership in the CFDMAS from 1987 to 1995. Records include correspondence, agendas, minutes, legal contracts, budget and financial working papers, reports and publications.
  For more information about this national organization, now named the Canadian Federation of Business School Deans, visit their website at "www.cfbsd.ca".
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1987 - 1988; F-42-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
    Creator's original file classification code: A.17.
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1987 - 1988; F-42-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - Correspondence, vol. 3, 1987 - 1988; F-42-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - CIDA, vol. 1, 1987 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - CIDA, vol. 2, 1987 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - Events, 1988; F-42-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - Minutes, 1988; F-42-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - China Management Education Program, vol. 1, 1988; F-42-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - China Management Education Program, vol. 2, 1988; F-42-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 42-26)
  - Contracts, 1988; F-42-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Institutional Evaluation of CFDMAS, vol. 1, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Institutional Evaluation of CFDMAS, vol. 2, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Correspondence, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Budget and administration, vol. 1, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Budget and administration, vol. 2, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Conferences and workshops, vol. 1, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Conferences and workshops, vol. 2, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 42-27)
  - Southeast Asia, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - Network initiatives - Latin America, Francophone Africa, S.E. Asia, South Asia (NAIR), vol. 1, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - Network initiatives - Latin America, Francophone Africa, S.E. Asia, South Asia (NAIR), vol. 2, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - CFDMAS/CLADEA management cooperation program, 1988 - 1989; F-42-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - Correspondence, 1989; F-42-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - Contracts, 1989; F-42-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 42-28)
  - Operational review, vol. 1, 1989 - 1991; F-42-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Operational review, vol. 2, 1989 - 1991; F-42-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Meetings and conferences, 1989 - 1991; F-42-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1990 - 1993; F-42-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1990 - 1993; F-42-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Meetings and conferences, vol. 1, 1993 - 1995; F-42-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Meetings and conferences, vol. 2, 1993 - 1995; F-42-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
  - Meetings and conferences, vol. 3, 1993 - 1995; F-42-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 42-29)
- International activities and linkages correspondence, 1985 - 1997; F-42-6; 18 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the development of student exchanges and business research partnerships with international business schools in Hong Kong, India, Malaysia, the United States, and Mexico. Records include correspondence, working papers, agendas, minutes, reports, financial working papers and publications.
  - Hong Kong, 1985 - 1997; F-42-6-1; 9 cm of textual records
    Hong Kong Baptist University
    - General correspondence, vol. 1, 1985 - 1993; F-42-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - General correspondence, vol. 2, 1985 - 1993; F-42-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Hong Kong Baptist University, vol. 1, 1991 - 1997; F-42-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Hong Kong Baptist University, vol. 2, 1991 - 1997; F-42-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Hong Kong Baptist University, vol. 3, 1991 - 1997; F-42-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Hong Kong Baptist University, vol. 4, 1991 - 1997; F-42-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
  - India (Narsee Monjee Institute), 1989 - 1993; F-42-6-2; 5 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1989; F-42-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-42-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-30)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-42-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1992 - 1993; F-42-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
  - Malaysia, 1992 - 1994; F-42-6-3; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-42-6-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1992 - 1994; F-42-6-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
  - USA/Canada/Mexico (Trilateral Exchange), 1993; F-42-6-4; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1993; F-42-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
- Publications, 1970 - 2004; F-42-7; 2.01 m of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by the Faculty of Business Administration. Records include annual scholarly activites reports, graduate student resume books, program and seminar pamphlets and related promotional materials, newsletters, student survival guides, discussion papers written by faculty, and student MBA project reports.
  The publications found in sub-series F-42-7-1 were aquired by the Archives from a variety of sources. Although the original accession of Business Administration records contained a number of departmental publications, most of the publications were collected by Archives staff as part of an artificial university-wide periodicals collection and then processed as part of the fonds.
  The source of the student MBA project reports found in this series is unknown as no supporting documentation exists in the Archives. The records were formally processed after being found with an accompanying box/file list. For unknown reasons, these MBA projects (dating 1970-1977, 121 in total) were not in the MBA Projects and Thesis database maintained by the SFU Library. As of 2006, a retroactive cataloging project is being undertaken to include these reports in the central Library database (seachable by author, title, and date) while the original copies of the records will remain in the Archives.
  - Departmental publications, 1977 - 2004; F-42-7-1; 38 cm of textual records
    - Chevron Endowed Chair in Management, [198-?]; F-42-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-31)